Finding Aid for the Milton L. Goldstein Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Milton L. Goldstein Collection
1933-1978
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0174
.42 linear feet
Biography/History
Milton L. Goldstein was a 1937 Vanderbilt University graduate. He died in 1976
Scope and Contents
This collection contains 11 file folders with correspondence, holiday greeting cards, newsletter, newspaper clippings, one photograph, programs, and various memorabilia belonging to Milton L. Goldstein.
- Correspondence - Incoming
  - From National Publishers Association, January 16, 1934
- Correspondence – Class of 1937
  - Class of 1937 to Chancellor Alexander Heard, February 15, 1972
  - Jack to Milton Goldstein w/Reunion Guest List, July 14, 1972
  - Class of 1937, n.d.
- Correspondence – Mrs. Goldstein
  - Mrs. Milton Goldstein to Chancellor Alexander Heard, October 31, 1978
- Holiday Greeting Cards
  - from The Alexander Heards, December 15, 1971
  - Madison Sarratt, Dean of Alumni, n.d.
- Memorabilia
  - Alumni Association Stickers (3), n.d.
  - Chapel Absence Slip, n.d.
  - Matriculation Card, 1933-1934
  - Meal Ticket, n.d.
  - Miscellaneous Receipts (3), 1933 and 1934
  - Permit to Enter, College of Arts and Science, September 26, 1933
  - Schedule and Recitations and Examinations, 1933-1934
  - X-Ray Requisition, May 1, 1935
- Newsletter
  - Commodore Comments, 1971
- Newspaper Clippings
  - Vanderbilt Glee Club, 1934
  - Vanderbilt Sports, 1960 & 1970s
  - Class of 1937 Reunions, 1962 and 1967
  - Committee for Vanderbilt, 1967
- Photographs
  - note on back Pittsburgh Vanderbilt Get-together
- Programs
  - The Men’s Glee Club, April 4, 1934
  - The Men’s Glee Club and The Women’s Glee Club, May 1, 1934